spanjobs.com 2012-10-03

# None

       • the said Website user-friendly and  comfortable  
       • you feel secure while submitting information to SpanJobs.com  
       • itself and the website accessible and invites  your questions or concerns about the website  
       • it known to you  that by using SpanJobs.com’s  websites you are consenting to the collection of certain data

**Information - collected or may be collected from you**  
SpanJobs.com will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through its  Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies," sent to your browser from a 

  *        • web server cookie stored on your hard drive 
  *        • an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use 
  *        • the domain server through which you access SpanJobs.com’s service 
  *        • the type of computer you're using
  *        • the type of web browser you're using 

SpanJobs.com may collect the following personally identifiable information about you: 

  *        • name including first, middle and last name 
  *        • alternate email address 
  *        • mobile/land line phone number and contact details 
  *        • ZIP/Postal code 
  *        • demographic profile (like your age, date of birth, gender, occupation, education, address and durables owned); 
  *        • preferences and interests (such as news, sports, travel and so on); 
  *        • financial information (like account or credit card numbers); and 
  *        • opinions of features on SpanJobs.com’s websites. 

SpanJobs.com may also collect the following information: 

  *        • about the pages you visit/access 
  *        • the links you click on SpanJobs.com’s site
  *        • the number of times you access the page 

You can terminate the usage of your account at any time. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.

**Collection of information**  
SpanJobs.com will collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit our site.

SpanJobs.com will collect personally identifiable information about you only as part of a voluntary registration process, on-line survey, or contest or any combination thereof.

SpanJobs.com’s advertisers may collect anonymous traffic information from their own assigned cookies to your browser.

SpanJobs.com’s website contains links to other Web sites. SpanJobs.com are not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites which SpanJobs.com does not own, manage or control.

SpanJobs.com may make chat rooms, forums, instant messenger and message boards and other services available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. SpanJobs.com has no control over its use and you should exercise caution when disclosing your personal information to anyone.

 **Use of information**  
SpanJobs.com uses your personal information to: 

  *        • provide personalized features to you 
  *        • customise SpanJobs.com’s sites to your interest 
  *        • contact you whenever required 
  *        • provide the services requested by you
  *        • preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy

SpanJobs.com uses contact information internally to: 

  *        • direct SpanJobs.com’s efforts for product/service improvement 
  *        • contact you as a survey respondent 
  *        • intimate you if you win any contest; and
  *        • provide promotional materials to you from its contest sponsors or advertisers

Generally, SpanJobs.com uses anonymous traffic information to: 

  *        • remind us of who you are in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service from both an advertising and an editorial perspective; 
  *        • recognize your access privileges to our Web sites 
  *        • track your entries in some of our promotions, sweepstakes and contests to indicate a player's progress through the promotion and to track entries, submissions, and status in prize drawings 
  *        • make sure that you don't see the same ad repeatedly 
  *        • help diagnose problems with our server 
  *        • administer our Web sites
  *        • track your session so that we can understand better how people use our sites

**Information sharing**  
SpanJobs.com will not use your financial information for any purpose other than to complete a transaction with you. 

SpanJobs.com will  not rent, sell or share your personal information and it will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless: 

  *        • SpanJobs.com has your permission 
  *        • it is to provide products or services requested by you 
  *        • it is to assist in conducting investigation, preventing or taking action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person, violations of SpanJobs.com’s Terms of Use or to defend against legal claims;
  *        • special circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure.

SpanJobs.com will share your information with advertisers on an aggregate basis only.

**Available options regarding collection, use and distribution of your information**  
Supplying personally identifiable information is entirely voluntary

However, SpanJobs.com reserves the right to send to you certain service related communication, considered to be a part of your SpanJobs.com account without offering you the facility to opt-out. You may update your information and change your account settings at any time.

Upon request, SpanJobs.com will remove/block your personally identifiable from the view of public website usage or resume search, thereby canceling your registration/membership. See Contact information below. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account. 

If SpanJobs.com  proposes to use your personally identifiable information for any commercial purposes, it will notify you at the time we collect that information and allow you to opt-out of having your information used for those purposes.

You can accept or decline the cookies. All sites that are customizable require that you accept cookies. You also must accept cookies to register as someone for access to some of our services. For information on how to set your browser to alert you to cookies, or to reject cookies, go to http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq/.

**Security procedures to protect information from loss, misuse or alteration**  
SpanJobs.com has in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect against loss, misuse and alteration of the information under SpanJobs.coms control., For example, SpanJobs.com’s servers are accessible only to authorized personnel and that your information is shared with respective personnel on need to know basis to complete the transaction and to provide the services requested by you.

Although we will endeavor to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this site, you agree that SpanJobs.com will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized acts of third parties, unavoidable circumstances or special circumstances.

**Correction of inaccuracies in the information**  
You can undertake online correction or updation of any information provided by you to SpanJobs.com. In the event of loss of access details you can use the following option: 

  *        • Send an e-mail to [CustomerCare@ **Spanjobs**.com](mailto:CustomerCare@Spanjobs.com "mailto:CustomerCare@Spanjobs.com")

****Policy** updates**  
SpanJobs.com reserves the right to change or update this **Privacy** **Policy** at any time. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon being posted on this site.

You can offer your views, suggestions, if any, by mailing us at [CustomerCare@ **Spanjobs**.com](mailto:CustomerCare@Spanjobs.com "mailto:CustomerCare@Spanjobs.com").
